你原来的服务生去休息了
You waitress just went on break,
我只是个爱穿聚酯热狗装
and I'm just someone who like dressing
打酱油的路人
as a polyester hotdog,
所以等你要结账时再喊我吧
so I'll take that whenever you are ready.
给  慢慢结吧
There you go, no rush.
好的  拉杰夫·古德康达先生
Ok, mister Rajeev Gudikanda.
不得不说  你这小把戏
I have to say, that's a pretty gutti scheme
很"古德"啊
you got going there,
但我"康达"不信
but I guttikonda don't believe it.
你什么意思呢
What are you saying there?
波士顿老兄  你问你我是什么意思
What am I saying there, Boston?
我相信你窝在你妈家地下室的
I'm saying I believe you watched Slumdog Millionaire
肮脏沙发上看过《贫民窟的百万富翁》
on a sticky couch in your mom's basement,
但打死我也不信你是印度人
but I'm not buying that you're Indian.
带着你的假波士顿东区印度口音滚出去
So take your fake, east Boston, indian accent out of here,
不然我就叫警察来
or I'll call the cops.
兄弟  偷了信用卡还来这破餐厅吃
Dude, stolen credit card, and you choose to eat here?
这才是大罪啊
That's the real crime.
拉杰夫
Hey, Rajeev.
拉杰夫  我的好兄弟
Rajeev, my man.
拉杰夫·古德康达
Rajeev Gudikanda.
这样吧  这顿我请
You know what? This one's on me.
我这人有信任无能的病
I have trust issues.
真奇怪  居然还剩了三个红丝绒小蛋糕
That's weird. We still have three red velvets left.
那个催吐妹今天没来吧
I guess that bulimic girl didn't come in today.
她来了啊  在厕所里吐呢
No, she's here. She's in the bathroom.
如果我帮她保留了
Hmm, if I save these for her,
这算是帮她还是害她呢
would that be helping or hurting?
大家好啊
Hey, everybody.
说到烦[害]
Speaking of hurting,
最让我烦的人来了
Here comes a pain in my ass.
阿憨  你要最后一个红丝绒吗
Han, do you want the last red velvet?
另外两个要留给催吐妹
The other two are for the bulimic girl.
我做了决定
I made the call.
我不再吃小蛋糕了
No more cupcakes for me.
我在做六天的果汁排毒疗程
I've been on a juice cleanse for six days.
阿憨要猎艳
Han's on the prowl,
必须保持紧实体态啊
and I got to keep this body tight, son.
我也是约会池里的泡妞大将呢
I'm in the dating pool, you know.
儿童潜水池吗
Yeah, the shallow end.
你知道排毒疗程一点屁用都没有吧
You know those cleanses never work, right?
是吗  那你怎么解释这个
Really? Then how do you explain this?
我不知道
I don't know.
是要我摸摸肚皮然后许愿吗[弥勒佛]
Am I supposed to rub it and make a wish?
生过三孩子的妈来说  你身材不错哦
Not bad for having three kids, Han.
啥  你们没瞧见我的腹肌吗
What? You don't see my abs coming in?
我看见了一团大腹肌
I see one large ab coming in.
这起码也有两块
That's at least a two-pack.
阿憨  图派克本人都比你那两块还生龙活虎
Han, the real Tupac is more alive than your two-pack.
我要把这最后一块当免费试吃样品
I'm gonna give this last cupcake away as a free sample.
我最近的推广微薄反映好像不太好
My promotional tweets haven't been getting much love lately.
你说啥了
What'd you say?
你提到跟工作有关的词我就大脑断电
I black out whenever you use work words.
什么
What?
姑娘们  送你们
Here you go, ladies,
免费请你们吃个麦克斯自制小蛋糕
a Max's homemade cupcake on the house.
不用了  谢谢
Nah, I'm cool.
我要把我今天的
I'm saving my calories
卡路里配额留给超酷的新牛角圈
for one of those fabulous new cronuts.
而且小蛋糕已经过时了
Plus, cupcakes are so over.
《绽放》也过气超久啊
Well, so is Blossom, but...
但你们还不是照穿里面的衣服
it didn't stop you from wearing that outfit.
那俩权力归花儿的贱货
Those flower power skanks over there--
"权力归花儿的贱货"
"Flower power skanks."
你看  说这种词我大脑就不会断电了
See, these are words I recognize and hear.
她说她只想要什么牛角圈
Anyway, she said she only cares about cronuts
还说小蛋糕过时了
and that cupcakes are over.
小蛋糕是不朽经典对吧
Cupcakes are classic, right?
别听她们放屁
Don't listen to them.
她们穿着高腰牛仔裤呢
They're wearing high-waisted jeans.
女性牛仔裤能被穿到这么高的唯一时刻
The only time I like seeing women's jeans that high
只有阿憨被我玩拉高内裤套头时
is when I'm giving Han a wedgie.
而且什么是牛角圈啊
Also, what's a cronut?
克罗蛋[音似]是我克罗埃西亚那个
Cronut is what we called my Croatian cousin
独蛋侠表哥的绰号
with one testicle.
他后来上吊自杀了
He hung himself.
好吧  在美国
Okay, well, in America,
那是指牛角面包与甜甜圈的混合体
it's a half-croissant, half-doughnut.
是目前最热门的话题
People can't stop talking about them.
如果牛角圈能说话
If cronuts had tongues,
那它大概就是甜品界的麦莉·赛勒斯
they'd be the Miley Cyrus of pastries.
有道理  听起来蠢爆了
You're right. They sound stupid.
蠢到超美味啊  哪里可以买到
Stupid delicious. Where can I get one?
只有在SOHO区一家甜品店有卖
You can only get them at this one pastry shop in SOHO,
很多人半夜4点就开始排队呢
And people start lining up at 4:00 A.M.
哎哟  时代在改变啊
Boy, times do change.
以前半夜4点  人们只会"吸一排"[毒品]
Back in the day, 4:00 A.M. was when people would snort lines,
而不是"站一排"
not stand in 'em.
谁这么闲能有空排队一整天
Who has the time to wait in line all day
就为了买一块白痴甜品啊
for a piece of lame pastry?
大家好啊
Hey, everyone.
我买到了牛角圈
I got a cronut.
我排了足足两天呢
I waited in line for two whole days.
苏菲  你也在赶这股潮流啊
Sophie, you bought into the hype too?
废话  你明知道姐永远走在潮流尖端
Oh, come on, you know your girl Sophie is always on trend.
我是第一个穿洞洞鞋的人呢
I was the first one wearing Crocs.
美国的洞洞鞋潮流就是我传来的
I brought the Crocs craze to America.
我有钱那会  我送了一万双洞洞鞋
When I was rich, I sent 10,000 pairs of Crocs
给非洲孩子穿
to children in Africa.
好让他们看起来像傻逼吗
Why, to make them less cool?
你们看  这张是我在排队
Look, girls, here I am in the cronut line.
这张我也还在排
And here I am still in line.
这张是我骑一只小象
Oh, and--oh, and here I am riding a baby elephant.
这张就是我吃着牛角圈啦
and here I am eating a cronut.
麦克斯  虽然这东西蠢爆了  我们还是得去
Max, as stupid as it is, we've got to go over there.
去了解一下  什么是人家有而我们没有的
We need to figure out what they have that we don't.
我现在就能回答你
Oh, I'll tell you what they have.
是牛角圈
Cronuts.
天啊  瞧这队排得
Oh, my God. Look at this line.
我早说了我们应该早点过来
I knew we should have gotten here sooner,
但某人要装好人
but, no, I had to be a good person,
要帮忙人家把
I had to carry that torso man
滑滑板的假人给搬上地铁楼梯
on the skateboard up the subway stairs.
排这么长  就为了吃牛角面包加甜甜圈
All this is for a croissant and a doughnut?
这俩东西早就发明了
Those things already existed.
我当年混合了事后避孕药与安眠药时
Where was all the fanfare when I combined the sleeping pill
我的广大粉丝热潮都上哪去了
with the morning after pill and called it
那药我命名为"事后睡一觉避孕药"
the "sleep-through- the-morning-after" Pill?
这东西怎么会这么火爆啊
How did these things get so popular?
潮流本来就是很不科学的东西
There's no science to this trend stuff.
就只是某个死贱基男
It's all decided by one bitchy gay guy
在房里瞎掰报道捧起来的
typing in his room, making it all up.
那我们得研究一下这潮流啊
Well, then we have to do some trend research.
得研究出怎么样把
We've got to figure out how to make
麦克斯自制小蛋糕捧成下一个牛角圈
Max's homemade cupcakes the next cronuts.
我烦死这些潮流商品了
I hate all these stupid trends.
排毒  牛角圈  避孕套
Cleanses, cronuts, condoms.
先生  打扰一下
Excuse me, sir,
我叫卡洛琳
My name's Caroline.
我是一个潮流分析员
I'm a trend researcher.
我叫查克  卖磁铁的
I'm Chuck. I sell magnets.
是什么原因让你排队一整天
What made you want to spend an entire day
只为了买到牛角圈
in line for cronuts?
我喜欢牛角面包  也喜欢甜甜圈
I like croissants. I like doughnuts.
我还是个胖子  不言自明了吧
I'm a fat guy. It all adds up.
的确  你是个胖子没错
That's true. You are a fat guy.
对街就有一家甜甜圈店
And there's a doughnut shop right across the street.
你为啥不去那边一趟  买个甜甜圈呢
So why don't you just stop there, get a damn doughnut,
也拯救你於之前那200步
and save yourself the last 200
随时都可能倒下的路程呢
possibly life-threatening steps to here?
这东西把我两个所爱食物合二为一
Look, it's two things I like put together.
还需要解释吗
End of story.
就是这个  麦克斯
That's it, Max.
重点在合二为一
It's the two things together.
单纯一个已经不够了
One thing isn't enough anymore.
所以奥列格的表哥才上吊自杀啊
Yeah, that's why Oleg's cousin hung himself.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
你上一次只做一件事是什么时候
When's the last time you did just one thing?
比如没一边看电影
Like, watch a movie
一边在玩手机
without playing a game on your phone?
看《魔力麦克》时
Magic Mike.
等等  边看边"玩自己"算吗
Wait, does playing with yourself count?
走吧  我们去最后面排队吧
Come on, let's get to the end of the line.
最后面排队
End of the line?
那是新手干的事
That's for rookies.
我是排队大师
I'm a line pro.
我和我妈总需要排队等食品救济劵
My mom and I waited in line for food stamps,
演唱会场外草地位
Bob Seger lawn seats.
不过我们有个周六在"枪换钱"活动排了一天
We spent a Saturday in the "Guns for cash" line.
因为那个队绝对不能随便插
Now that's a line you don't want to cut in.
跟着我
Follow my lead.
兄弟  排队买牛角圈呢
Hey, man, cronut line.
买完之后打算干嘛
What do you want to do after this?
好啦  行行行  我们去最后
Okay, all right, all right. Back of the line.
大家别激动
Everybody relax.
原来我的插队技术
Guess my mom being topless
影响力远没有我妈裸上身来得大啊
had more to do with my line skills than I thought.
这下好了  你看着牛角圈排队人潮
Oh, great. Look at the cronut line.
我早说了我们应该早点过来
I told you we should have left sooner,
但你说不行  我们得待在庙里
but, no, you said we had to stay at temple.
你可是拉比啊[犹太教导师]
You're the rabbi.
我会去当全都是你逼的
Yeah, a career I was forced into
因为某人想写一本回忆录
because someone wanted to write his memoir.
盖瑞  你是被领养的  大家知道了
We get it, Garry. You're adopted.
亲  往前走啊  队伍都往前挪了
Move up, hon. You gotta fill the gap.
你别挤上来我  我就会往前走了
I would if you would stop trying to fill my gap.
这有啥差别啊
What difference does it make?
往不往前走  等的时间还是一样
You're still gonna have the same amount of time to wait.
而30年后
And then, in 30 years,
我们也全都是要死于无线网癌的
we're all gonna die from wi-fi cancer.
好了  大家平心静气
Okay, let's all just take a breath.
我们还得在这排上好一会呢
It looks like we're gonna be here for a while.
你说得对
You know what? You're right.
我叫洁瑞
Hi, I'm Jerri.
我叫盖瑞
And I'm Garry.
我是洁瑞  他是盖瑞
I'm Jerri, he's Garry.
我高  他矮
I'm tall, he's small.
有爱吧  这是我们的特色
Cute, right? That's our thing.
我叫卡洛琳  她叫麦克斯
I'm Caroline, and this is Max.
就这样  我们没啥特色
That's it. We don't have a thing.
是什么吸引了你们来呢
So what drew you here today?
我们就是流行的弄潮儿
Oh, well, we're trend-chasers.
一有新东西开始流行  我们就得追
When something new hits, we are on it
比如那些海盐黑巧克力啊
like sea salt on dark chocolate.
优格吧
We did Pinkberry,
氮气冰激凌丸  羽衣甘蓝  藜麦  茶菌
dippin' dots, kale, quinoa, Kombucha.
只要流行  我们必追
All the ka's. Just' cause.
看得出我们没有孩子吗
Can you tell we don't have kids?
她生不出
She couldn't.
盖瑞
Garry!
其实他说的是真的
Actually, it's true,
欲知详情  可以读他的回忆录
And you can read all about it in his memoir.
书名叫...
It's called...
好了  洁瑞  盖瑞
You know what? Jerri, Garry.
我们好像熟得太快了
I think we got too close too soon.
大家还是先保留点空间吧
Maybe we need a little space.
我们得赶紧插前面去
We got to move up in line
不然跟他们在一起没完没了
to get away from these people.
需要我露奶吗
Should I just take my top off?
-下一个  -终于啊
- Next in line. - It happened!
终于排到最前面了
We made it to the front of the line!
我们是领头人
We're the front people!
Yeah, we're the front people!
后排人都是傻逼
Back people suck!
不是不是  我是说"后排人"不是"黑人"[音似]
No, no, I said "back people," "back people."
赞美上帝[犹太教祝福语]
Baruch hashem.
我们都爱看《白宫管家》
We loved The Butler.
我们一起经历了不少
You know, we've been through a lot.
剑拔弩张  唇枪舌战
Tempers flared, things were said.
我很确定队伍后面那个荷兰人挂了
I'm fairly certain that Dutch guy back there died.
但我们终于排到了  你们也是好人
But we made it, and you guys are good people.
跟海盐一样好的好人
The sea salt of the earth.
-谁是下一个  -我们
- Who's next? - We are.
我们只能接待两位顾客
I can only take a party of two.
-你们四个是一起的吗  -不是
- Are all four of you together? - Nope.
完全不认识他们
We don't know them.
-你们...  -甩开她们  盖盖
- Guys? - Cut 'em loose, Gar.
全卖完了  我们要打烊了
All sold out. We're closed.
我知道你是被当面包店门童的
I know you're driven mad with the power of being
权力冲昏头脑  但也别这么绝吧
a doorman at a bakery, but come on!
麦克斯  你知道我现在最想要什么吗
Max, you know what I want more than anything?
杀了洁瑞与盖瑞吗
To kill Jerri and Garry?
我绝对支持你
'Cause I'm totally on board.
不  我是想我们的生意也有人排队
No, I want our business to have a line.
我也想卖光光
I want to sell out.
我想要别人也能为了抢我们产品而反目成仇
I want people to turn against each other for our product.
行啊  我说了我能露奶
Again, I could just take my top off.
我知道  谢谢你
I know, and thank you.
让我们有这个秘密武器
We have that in our back pocket.
但我有个能先试试的主意
But I have an idea we can try first.
我准备要说公事用语了  听好啦  贱货
I'm gonna use work words now, so listen up, skank.
我在听
I'm listening.
我读了《华尔街日报》
I read in The Wall Street Journal
里面说到分类广告网站上有牛角圈黑市
that there's a whole black market for cronuts On Craigslist.
分类广告网  不行
Craigslist? Oh, no.
我没这么想吃到愿意再让
I don't want one bad enough to let some guy
变态男舔我腋下一小时了
lick my armpit for an hour again.
不是我们俩吃
They're not for us.
是放到店里卖
We'll sell them at our window,
好吸引客人嘛
just to attract attention,
等牛角圈卖光了
and then, when they sell out,
我们就轻松继续卖他们小蛋糕
we'll effortlessly switch to cupcakes.
经典的偷圈换糕之计
Classic bake and switch.
为了这傻逼潮流  这么费劲吗
All that work for some stupid fad?
我是说"潮流"
I said "fad."
我们都很爱《烛台背后》哦
We loved Behind the Candelabra.
再给他发短信试试
Try texting him again.
他已经迟到15分钟了
He's 15 minutes late.
你居然相信一个在分类广告网站上
You're really surprised that a guy reselling pastries
"发牢骚"那区的转卖甜点的男人
in the "Rants and raves" section of Craigslist
会是守时的类型
isn't the punctual type?
真是太令人兴奋了
This is so exciting.
我以前从来没在"黑"市上买过任何东西
I've never bought anything on the black market before.
我甚至不敢去
I'm still afraid to go to that
转角那个菲律宾市场
Filipino market around the corner.
你是那个人吗
Are you the guy?
我不知道  你是那个妞吗
I don't know. Are you the girl?
靠  这两句台词好烂
So far, this musical sucks.
暗号是什么
What's the password?
牛角圈
Cronut.
"1234"这种被别人用了吗
Was "1234" already taken?
"去门那碰头"
Meet us by the door.
就是去门那碰头的暗号
Which is code for, meet us by the door.
也是你"想暗号水平超烂"的暗号
Which is code for, "You're really bad at code."
好啦  我们先说下计划
Okay, let's talk about our plan.
我们一个唱红脸一个唱白脸
It's a classic good cop/bad cop.
我管那人订了10个牛角圈
I'm gonna ask the guy for ten cronuts,
他会跟我要250块
and he's gonna quote me 250.
好  然后我就唱红脸  装作勃然大怒
Right, then I play bad cop and act outraged.
然后我来唱白脸  最后以200块成交
And then I play good cop, and we settle at 200.
好的  你不用担心我的演技
Yeah, and don't worry about me.
我到时候会现场即兴加些料
I'll improv some good stuff on the spot.
你确定不用先在我面前试试吗
Are you sure you don't want to run it by me first?
我在沃顿商学院时  曾是即兴表演组的一员
I was in an improv group at Wharton.
我们组叫"搞笑的1%"
We were called "The fun percent."
我觉得我就跟其他
And I can imagine myself not laughing
99%的观众一样笑不出来
With 99% of the audience.
我们速战速决
Let's make it quick.
你们不是这城里唯一想要我圈[蛋蛋]的妞
You're not the only girls in town who want my nuts!
你是说你的牛角圈吧
I assume you mean cronuts.
不  我还是一名男妓
No, I'm also a male prostitute.
先验货吧
Let's see the product.
她说的是其他可以"吃"的货
She meant the other baked goods.
你们得把话说清楚点
You got to be clear.
清一色的好货色
Pretty maids, all in a row.
让老娘尝一口
Let Mama get a taste.
口感很纯  10个多少钱
That's pure. How much for ten?
我知道之前是开价250块  但...
I know I said 250 earlier, but...
胡扯  给你150块  不卖拉倒  贱人
Bullcrap! 150 or we walk, bitch!
好啦  大家冷静点
Okay, let's all just calm down.
这笔买卖真的很划算  麦克斯
It's a really good deal, Max.
不如我们各让一步  200块怎么样
How about we settle at 200 and call it a night?
对  对  关于价格方面
Yeah, yeah, yeah. About that.
今晚好多人想跟我高价买呢
I be getting mad offers for these things tonight.
我要加价到300块  不买拉倒
I actually got to raise it to 300, or I walk.
贱人
Bitch.
哎哟  哟  你的手好冰
Ooh, ow, ow, ooh, your hands are cold.
你刚叫我什么
What'd you call me?
-没什么  -我也这么认为
- Nothing. - That's what I thought.
她刚说200块  我们就给你200块
She said 200. We'll pay 200.
而且你要乖乖收下
And you'll take it.
你要把钱塞进你穿着的这件"恒适女士"帽衫
You'll shove it in this Hanes Her Way hoodie you're wearing,
跟我说  "谢谢你  麦克斯"
you'll say, "thank you, Max"
然后你就会滚出去  知道了吗
And you'll hit the bricks, capisce?
卡洛琳  钱
Caroline, cash.
-谢谢你  麦克斯  -你说什么
- Thank you, Max. - What'd you say?
谢谢你  麦克斯
Thank you, Max!
我被吓得打寒颤  你们这里有热茶吗
I've got the chills now. Do you guys serve tea?
我这红脸唱得怎么样
How's that for bad cop?
太精彩了
Riveting.
我还以为自己在看美剧《特殊受害者之蛋糕店特辑》
I felt like I was watching SVU: bakery edition.
好了  这是最后一个了
Okay, here we go. This is the last one.
你想要这个牛角圈吗
You want this cronut?
把你衣服撩起来我看看
Lift up your shirt and let me see 'em.
去把阿憨抓过来
Go get Han.
我要给他看看什么是真正的腹肌
I want to show him what an ab is.
麦克斯  你真该去看看那队伍
Max, you should see the line.
都排到街区的一半了
It's halfway down the block.
也有人为我们排队了  计划奏效了
We have a line. It's working.
但现在要怎么办
But what's gonna happen now?
某年圣诞  我在塔吉特百货工作
I worked at Target the Christmas
当"挠痒娃娃"卖完时
they ran out of tickle me Elmo,
场面可是相当血腥啊
and there was so much blood.
按原定计划
As planned,
我们只需淡定换上我们美味的小蛋糕
we'll just calmly switch to our delicious cupcakes,
然后坐等卖光光
and then those'll sell out too
因为小蛋糕也很好吃啊
Because they're that good.
看我的
Okay.
各位  注意了
Attention, everyone.
各位  请注意啦
Everyone, can I have your attention?
我们非常抱歉
Actually, we are very sorry,
但牛角圈已经卖完了
but we are now sold out of cronuts.
但是我们还有更好吃的
We do, however, have something even better--
麦克斯自制小蛋糕
Max's homemade cupcakes.
好吧  走吧走吧
All right, go!
离开这  去追逐白痴的潮流去吧
Leave. Chase your stupid trends.
但我们一点都不担心  小蛋糕才是最经典的
But we're not worried! Cupcakes are classic!
我们是业界的奥黛丽亚赫本
We're Audrey Hepburn!
麦克斯  小蛋糕过时了
Max, cupcakes are over.
你知道为什么吗
And you know why?
因为小蛋糕只是一样事物
Because cupcakes are just one thing.
如果我们能把两样事物合二为一  就不得了了
If we had two things, then we'd be something.
说得对  我打电话给卖家
That does it. I'm calling the dealer.
我觉得我们不该再买牛角圈了
I don't think we should order more cronuts.
不  我说的卖家是我的药头
Oh, no, I mean my drug dealer.
我要舒缓下压力
I need to take the edge off.
真郁闷  我把假人摔地上那会
This sucks. I feel worse about myself
都没这么自我感觉糟糕
than I did when I dropped the torso man.
你拿那些薯条干嘛呢
What are you doing with those fries?
我拿它们沾糖霜呢
I'm dipping 'em in frosting.
我每次不开心都这么吃
I do it when I'm depressed.
我直接从婴儿食品升级到糖霜薯条
I went right from baby food into fries in frosting.
会好吃吗  看起来很恶心啊
Is it good? It looks disgusting.
又好吃又恶心  你尝尝
It is both. Just taste it.
的确挺好吃的
These are pretty good.
又甜又咸  小蛋糕和薯条
Sweet and salty. Cupcakes and fries.
那是两样事物
That's two things.
蛋糕薯条  我们要挣大钱了
Cake fries. We're millionaires.
我什么都吃的爱好终于有回报了
My willingness to eat anything finally pays off!
慢着  你确定我们不是病急乱投医吗
Wait, are you sure it's not just us being desperate?
就像亚当·莱文在布鲁克林录MV时
Like, when Adam Levine made that music video in Brooklyn
那天你湿身穿着紧身背心  从人家场景里不断来回走
and you walked past the set all day in a wet tank top?
反正试试[露出]也无伤大雅
It can't hurt to put them out there.
那天你也是这么说的
That's what you said that day too.
你就乖乖坐下来嘛  阿憨
Just sit down for a second, Han.
但现在正值上班之际呢
But this is the middle of a shift.
如果你不乖乖坐下
I'm gonna tell everyone
我就告诉大家  你现在正值
you're in the middle of a male-to-female shift
"由男变女"之际
if you don't sit down.
好啦
All right.
今晚邀你们来是尝尝下一样热门事物[大物]
You are here tonight to taste the next big thing.
你们为啥要对我说我的泡妞金句呢
Okay, now you're just repeating my pick-up lines back to me.
才不是  我说的是新甜点
No, it's a new dessert,
我们组了一个完美的典型群众小组
and we've assembled the perfect focus group--
黑人  猪  健康脑残粉
A black man, a pig, and a health fanatic.
你们各自对号入座吧
Y'all know who you are.
我最近的确是试着吃健康一点
I suppose I have been trying to eat better lately.
号外  号外  各位注意了
Hey, extra, extra! Read all about it!
我现在是双性恋啦
I'm bisexual now!
完美  我们现在又有LGBTQ群体代表来加入
Oh, perfect, now we have the LGBTQ community represented.
-后面那个"Q"是什么  -疑问者
- What's the "Q"? - Questioning.
他已回答
And answered.
各位  这位是维罗尼卡
Hey, everybody. Meet Veronica.
她是漂亮的黑人  头发还是金色的短发
She's cute, she's black, she has short blonde hair,
她很令人性奋
She's exciting.
我们是在灵魂周期课上认识的
And we met in soul cycle class.
没错
Yes, we did.
她的汗水害我摔跤   就送了我一根能量棒道歉
I slipped in her sweat and she bought me a Luna bar.
现在  你现在才玩双性恋
Now? Now you're bisexual?
没错  我要紧跟现在的"双"潮流
Well, yeah, you got to keep up with the trends.
好了  各位群体
Okay, focus group.
大家听我说
Let's focus.
这是我们开发的新产品  叫蛋糕薯条
This is our new product, called cake fries.
很可爱吧
Cute, right?
只需从左边拿一根薯条
You just take a fry from the left side,
沾到右边蛋糕的糖霜上
dip it into the cupcake frosting on the right,
然后就慢慢享受这美味可口的甜点吧
and enjoy your sweet, yet savory dessert.
这女人是很认真地在教我怎么吃东西吗
Is this woman seriously trying to teach me how to eat food?
不要  这看起来一吃就会发胖
Oh, no, this looks very fattening,
我现在在断食呢
and I've been on a fast.
"舔"一口又不会死
One lick isn't going to kill you.
对啊  你问苏菲就知道了
Yeah, just ask Sophie.
好吧  就一口
Okay, one bite.
我不想你们保留任何意见
Now I don't want any of you to hold back.
我希望你们能诚实地作出评价
be completely honest in your criticism.
-我觉得  -闭嘴  阿憨
- Well, I feel like... - Shut up, Han.
不是啦  我是想说这很好吃
No, I was gonna say this is very good.
超级好吃
Too good.
别看我  姑娘们
Uh-oh, look away, girls.
你们把饿狼放出来了
You've released the kraken.
靠  真是太好吃了
Damn. That is tasty.
你们俩可能害我得了糖尿病
Now you may have given me diabetes,
因为我现在左脚没知觉了
as I have just lost the feeling in my left foot.
我觉得我可能会变成"三性恋"
You know what, I think I might be trisexual
因为我爱上了这些无性别的蛋糕薯条
because I'm having a love affair with these cake fries.
天啊  这太恶心了
Oh, my gosh, this is gross.
而且还黏糊糊的
And it's very messy.
拜托  那之前你吃我的时候怎么不说
Oh, come on, then what was earlier?
好了各位  你们的意见非常有用
Okay, everyone, this is all very helpful.
我们还在尝试中
We're still working some things out.
我的肚子感觉怪怪的
My tummy feels funny.
你是说你的腹肌处在疼吗
You mean your ab is hurting?
阿憨  你断食一周了  一开始要吃清淡点的
Han, your first food in a week probably shouldn't have been
而不是一大堆薯条和糖霜
A fistful of fries and frosting.
算了  各位  今天我们都很辛苦了
You know what, guys? We've all worked hard today.
今晚就这样吧
Let's call it a night.
但现在才9点
But it's only 9:00.
不好意思  我先走了
Pardon me. Excuse me.
这场面估计谁都不想看见
You don't want to see that.
注意闪开啦
Look out!
让开  快让开  不然就完了
Move it. Move it or lose it.
让开  不然我就完了
Move it or I lose it.
闪开  别挡着我
Out of my way, out of my way now!
哎哟妈呀
Oh, dear.
这比阿憨睡着时  奥列格在他脸上画鸡鸡
This is more embarrassing than when Han fell asleep
还要尴尬
and Oleg drew a penis on his face.
我把鸡鸡放他脸上然后描边而已
I traced that penis on his face.
你把薯条沾到糖霜里
Now you dip the fries in the frosting,
但我觉得吃这个最好的方式
but I find the best way to eat this
就等肚子里面空空如也的时候吃
is to first make sure you feel super empty inside.
绝对没问题
Not gonna be a problem.
真有爱
These are adorable.
你能帮我和它拍一张照吗
Could you please take a picture of me with it?
好可爱哦
It's so cute.
记得你把照片传上网时
And make sure you hashtag that picture
标签要写"麦克斯自制蛋糕薯条"
"Max's homemade cake fries" when you post it online.
忧郁的女孩居然对我们的蛋糕薯条露出微笑
A sad girl smiling with our cake fries.
一旦上了女性门户网站
Once that hits Ivillage,
我们就要被汹涌人潮压扁啦
we'll be knee-deep in Canvas Totes and Cankles.
给
Here you go!
抱歉  那是我们最后一份蛋糕薯条了
Sorry, that was our last cake fries.
明天我们会做多点的
We'll have more tomorrow.
慢着  都卖完了吗
Wait. We sold out?
我们售罄了
We sold out!
天啊  我们居然全卖光了
Oh, my god! We sold out!
太棒了  我做的甜点卖光光了  咱们去买飞机吧
Yes! I'm a sell-out! Let's buy a helicopter!
姑娘们
Hi, girls.
苏菲
Oh, hey, Sophie.
抱歉  但我们的蛋糕薯条卖完了
We're sorry, but we just ran out of cake fries.
没关系啦
Oh, that's fine by me.
我要回归基本喜好
I'm going back to the basics.
小蛋糕和鸡鸡
Cupcakes and penis.
给你小蛋糕  另一个喜好我们这没有
Here's your cupcake. We don't sell the other basic.
其实不用每5分钟
You know, it's nice to eat something
我想开了  麦克斯
You know what, Max?
无论是小蛋糕  牛角圈  还是蛋糕薯条
Cupcakes, cronuts, cake fries, whatever.
我们都会成功的  因为我们拥有
We're gonna be successful because we have the two things
最重要的两样事物  我和你
that really matter-- you and me.
我们有点像蛋糕薯条
We're kinda like cake fries.
又咸又甜
I mean, salty and sweet.
-我的甜的那个  -我是被"咸"湿佬袭击那个
- I'm sweet. - And I've been assaulted.